B1.
Nora's online friend, Carlos, is talking to her about summer in Brazil.
Listen to their conversation, underline the incorrect word in each sentence and write the correct one in the blank. Hi, Carlos.
How are you in Brazil? I'm fine.
It's summer in Brazil.
Summer here is from December to February.
It may get as hot as 40 degrees Celsius. Wow!
That's so hot! Yes.
You should stay in the shade when it's really hot.
Do you go to the beach?
I love swimming and playing on the beach in summer. Of course!
At weekends, my parents often take me to the beach.
We usually play volleyball and swim in the sea.
That sounds fun!
What's it like in Beijing?
Well, it's winter now.
It often snows in winter, but it's raining today.
It's very rainy in summer here too, but we play football every day, even in the rain.
I don't like to go out in the rain.
I hope the weather will be good tomorrow.